Jason M. Brunelle

jason@jasonbrunelle.com • (832) 499-1660 • Chicago, IL linkedin.com/in/jason-brunelle-18b6bb177 • github.com/jasonmb626 • jasonbrunelle.com

SUMMARY

Mid-career professional looking to move into a more technical direction. Recent graduate of a computer science program which honed and expanded technical skills developed over 20 years. Ready to switch tracks and work hard to apply knowledge to learn and expand skillsets and contribute to the success of an organization.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML/CSS/JavaScript(including Node.JS), C#.NET, Java

Frameworks: Express.JS, React.JS, Bootstrap CSS

Database: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, AWS, DynamoDB

Tools: AWS: Lamdbas, API Gateway, VCP, EC2

Git/GitHub, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code

Methodologies: Agile:Scrum

Office Tools: Excel (including VBA), Microsoft Word, Outlook

EDUCATION

University of Houston-Downtown, Houston, TX

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

GPA: 3.86

Honors: Summa Cum Laude

Relevant Coursework: Data Structures and Algorithms, Intro to Software Engineering, Network Security

Houston Community College, Houston, TX January 2015-May 2016

Associate in Arts

GPA: 4.0

Honors: 5 out of 5 semesters on Honors List, Graduated with Highest Honors Award

RELEVANT PROJECTS

Learning Management System, Houston, TX

Team Developer

- Collaborated with a team of 5 to build and code basic logic for Learning Management System that allowed students to register for classes, teachers to assign projects and submit grades, and displayed student GPA.
- Utilized C#.Net, Visual Studio, and MsSQL to develop project.

Texas House Witness Database, Chicago, IL

Solo Programmer

- Designed and implemented front-end in addition to back-end API and set up hosting on the cloud.
- Developed using Digital Ocean, Nginx, SSL, MySQL, Node.JS, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Excel, Visual Studio Code.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Landmark Theatres, Houston, TX

June 2009 – July 2019

January 2017-July 2019

General Manager

- Earned 3 promotions and 4 transfers during tenure due to accuracy, work ethic, people management, and inventory management abilities, actively utilizing technology to help achieve these results.
- Achieved a 5 year stretch of earning an average of 95.94% audit scores (all A's) after assuming management of mediocre location.
- Successfully created and maintained a customer-focused atmosphere that was inclusive of all team members which resulted in recognition by upper management, peers, and direct reports.
- Relied upon to conduct technical training (Projection/Point of Sale) at two other locations within the company.
- Assisted corporate office to improve official audit workbook through knowledge of Excel and VBA, saving an average of 5 hours manual work per month.